{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Which of the following is the agent associated with the development of neurodegenerative disease in livestock and humans?", "opta": "Prions", "optb": "Viroids", "optc": "virions", "optd": "Virinos", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "__________is probably the most important characteristic for classification of viruses in eukaryotes.", "opta": "Host preference", "optb": "Morphology", "optc": "Physical nature of virion constituents", "optd": "Chemical nature of virion constituents", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The __________ of the influenza-enveloped virus appear to be involved in attachment to the host cell receptor site.", "opta": "fimbriae", "optb": "flagellae", "optc": "hemagluttinin", "optd": "neuraminidase", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Intracellular structures formed during many viral infections, called __________ , which can directly disrupt cell structure.", "opta": "prokaryotes", "optb": "chromosomal disruptions", "optc": "inclusion bodies", "optd": "cytocidal bodies", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Viral RNA is replicated in the host cell", "opta": "cytoplasmic matrix", "optb": "nucleus", "optc": "mitochondria", "optd": "lysozomes", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which family has received most interest in their development as a biological control agent against insects?", "opta": "Reoviridae", "optb": "Baculoviridae", "optc": "Iridoviridae", "optd": "Poxviridae", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In cancer, the reversion of cells to a more primitive or less differentiated state is called", "opta": "neoplasia", "optb": "anaplasia", "optc": "metastasis", "optd": "oncogenic", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following has been linked to Kaposi's sarcoma?", "opta": "Epstein-Barr virus", "optb": "Human T-cell lymphotropic virus", "optc": "Human papilloma virus", "optd": "Human herpes virus 8", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Virulent and nonvirulent viruses may not", "opta": "inhibit host cell DNA synthesis", "optb": "inhibit host cell RNA synthesis", "optc": "stimulate host cell macromolecule synthesis", "optd": "degrade host cell DNA", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The hepadnaviruses such as hepatitis B virus are quite different from other DNA viruses with respect to genome replication. These replicate their DNA using", "opta": "DNA-dependent DNA polymerase", "optb": "reverse transcriptase", "optc": "Rnase H", "optd": "DNA ligase", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following virus is always detectable after infections?", "opta": "Hepatitis B virus", "optb": "Herpes simplex virus", "optc": "Varicella-zoster virus", "optd": "Cytomegalovirus", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Viroids are composed of", "opta": "single-stranded DNA", "optb": "double-stranded DNA", "optc": "single-stranded RNA", "optd": "double-stranded RNA", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}